Fine!
If you’re keeping these
rats, the wedding is dead!
Go tell Livia right
now  the wedding is off!
Exactly.
The engagement is over.
servants!
My lord, please …
Get the hell
out of my way!
A disowned failure
doesn’t deserve my daughter.
What?!
He’s disrespecting my family in public?!
I’ll handle this right now!
Severin, apologize!
Now!
They insulted my brothers first.
Why should I apologize?
Why are you being so stupid?!
This is your only
shot at a real future!
Ma’am, don’t worry.
It’s on me.
I’ll fix it.
My lord, I’m sorry.
We’re just stupid diggers
who didn’t know the rules.
We’re leaving right now.
Please don’t blame Severin.
David, stop!
You did nothing wrong!
Why are you begging these people?!
Severin, we know
you’re a good man.
Marrying a noble lady is your chance to finally rise.
You won’t have to
dig with us anymore.
Just remember us when you’re
living in a castle,
yeah?
I will,I promise.
Keep dreaming.
I’ve already told Livia
the wedding is canceled.
A disowned Carter bastard
has no claim on my daughter.
Fine.
Cancel it then.